http://www.bracepatt.com/content/privacy-notice

All Practices
All PracticesAntitrust / CompetitionCorporate & Securities-- Capital Markets-- Corporate Governance & Compliance-- Mergers, Acquisitions & Divestitures-- MLPsEducational InstitutionsEmployee Benefits / ERISAEnergy Regulations-- Commodities & Trading-- Compliance & Enforcement-- Electric Power-- Oil & Gas TransactionsEnvironmental Strategies-- Litigation & Enforcement Defense-- Natural Resource Protection-- Permitting & Regulation-- Pipeline Safety & Regulation-- Transaction Diligence & SupportFinancial Institutions-- Banking Compliance & Enforcement-- Mergers & AcquisitionsFinancial Restructuring-- Bankruptcy Litigation-- Creditors, Agents, Ad Hoc Groups and Official Committees-- Debtor Representation-- Distressed Energy-- Distressed M&A-- International Restructurings-- Maritime Investment and RestructuringGovernment Contracts-- Bid Protests-- Ethics/Compliance and Investigations-- False Claims Act-- Government Contract and Federal Grant Transactions-- Government Contracts Claims and Disputes Litigation-- GSA and VA Schedule Contracting-- Suspension and DebarmentGovernment Enforcement & Investigations-- Cybersecurity-- FCPA-- Internal Investigations-- MonitorshipsGovernment Relations-- Lobbying-- Political Law & Compliance CounselHealthcare & Life Sciences-- Healthcare Compliance & Operations-- Healthcare Financing & Transactions-- Healthcare Investigations & Enforcement-- Healthcare IP & Technology-- Healthcare LitigationIncident Prevention & Response-- Business Continuity Planning-- Crisis Communications-- Facilitating Emergency Drills & Tabletops-- OSHA/Workplace Safety-- Process Safety-- The Chemical Safety BoardInfrastructure & Development-- Digital Infrastructure-- Energy Infrastructure-- Social Infrastructure-- Transportation InfrastructureInsurance Recovery-- Placement Assistance, Policy Reviews and Program Audits-- Contractual Risk Management – Insurance Procurement and Indemnity Provisions-- Transactional Matters – Insurance Due Diligence and Reps and Warranties CoverageIntellectual Property-- Data Security and Privacy-- Patents-- Technology Transactions-- Trademark / CopyrightsLabor & Employment-- Agreements-- Class & Collective Actions-- Compliance-- Employment Litigation-- Immigration-- OSHA-- UnionsLending-- Asset-Based Lending-- Mezzanine Lending-- Project Finance-- Reserve-Based Lending-- Structured Finance, Commodities Finance & Derivative Products-- Syndicated LendingLitigation-- Appellate-- Construction Litigation-- Employment-- Energy Litigation-- Environmental Litigation-- Financial Institutions Litigation-- International Energy Disputes-- IP Litigation-- Renewable Energy Disputes-- Securities & Corporate Governance LitigationOil & Gas-- Exploration & Production-- Midstream-- Oil & Gas Private Equity-- Oil & Gas Trading & Marketing-- Refining & Petrochemicals-- Water IndustryOutsourcingPower-- Independent Power Producers-- Power Private Equity-- Power Trading & Marketing-- Regulated UtilitiesPrivate EquityPublic Finance-- Bond Counsel-- Disclosure Counsel-- Economic Development / Project Finance-- Securities Enforcement-- Tax Counsel-- Underwriter’s CounselReal Estate Investment & Finance-- Acquisitions & Divestitures-- Commercial & Mixed Use Development-- Leasing & Corporate Relocations-- Project Finance & Lending-- Public Private PartnershipsRenewable Energy & Sustainability -- Biomass-- Carbon Capture Utilization and Storage -- Energy Storage -- Hydrogen-- Hydropower-- Solar-- WindStrategic CommunicationsTaxTax Exempt Organizations
All Locations
All LocationsAustinConnecticutDallasDubaiHoustonLondonNew YorkSan AntonioSeattleWashington, DC
View Advanced SearchReset form
All Industries
All IndustriesEnergyFinanceHealthcareInfrastructureReal EstateTechnology
All Titles
All TitlesPartnerCounselAssociateNon-Attorney Consultant
All Bars
All Bars*Not licensed to practice in England and Wales*Not licensed to practice in New York*Not licensed to practice in Texas *Texas (Pending)Advocate, Rolls of the Bar Council of IndiaAttorney in South AfricaBarrister and Solicitor in Western Australia, AustraliaCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDistrict of ColumbiaGeorgiaIndianaLouisianaMadridMarylandMassachusettsMassachusetts (non-active member)MexicoMinnesotaNew JerseyNew MexicoNew South Wales, AustraliaNew YorkNorth CarolinaOklahomaPennsylvaniaPennsylvania (inactive)Registered Foreign Lawyer, Solicitors Regulation Authority, England and Wales Solicitor in New South Wales, AustraliaSolicitor in Queensland, Australia and Western AustraliaSolicitor in ScotlandSolicitor in South AustraliaSolicitor of the Senior Courts of England and WalesSolicitor, IrelandState Bar of Texas Foreign Legal ConsultantTexasU.S. Patent and Trademark OfficeU.S. Supreme CourtVirginiaWashingtonWashington, DC (non-active member)
All Languages
All LanguagesArabic — fluentBasic GermanBasic SpanishFrench — fluentSpanish — proficientAfrikaansArabicDanishEnglishFrenchGermanHebrewItalianKoreanNorwegian (fluent)RussianSpanishSwahili (fluent)Tamil
All Schools
All SchoolsAbilene Christian UniversityAlabama A&M UniversityAmerican UniversityAmerican University School of LawAmerican University, Washington College of LawAPTECHArizona State UniversityAuburn UniversityAustralian National University, Canberra, AustraliaBangalore UniversityBaylor Law SchoolBaylor UniversityBond UniversityBoston CollegeBoston UniversityBoston University School of LawBPP Business SchoolBPP Law School, LondonBPP Law School, UKBPP Law, Holborn, UKBPP Law, Manchester, UKBPP University CollegeBrigham Young UniversityBrooklyn Law SchoolBrown UniversityCalifornia State University, San MarcosCalifornia Western School of LawCardiff UniversityCarthage CollegeCatholic University of AmericaCatholic University of America, Columbus School of LawCoe CollegeColgate UniversityCollege of CharlestonCollege of LawCollege of Law, LondonCollege of Law, UKCollege of William & MaryColumbia CollegeColumbia Law SchoolColumbia UniversityColumbia University School of LawCornell Law SchoolCornell UniversityDartmouth CollegeDickinson CollegeDrew UniversityDuke UniversityDuke University School of LawElon UniversityEmory UniversityEmory University School of LawFairfield UniversityFlinders University of South AustraliaFordham UniversityFordham University School of LawFranklin Pierce Law CenterGeorge Mason University School of LawGeorge Washington University Law SchoolGeorgetown UniversityGeorgetown University Law CenterGolden State University School of LawGujarat UniversityHamilton CollegeHarvard CollegeHarvard Law SchoolHarvard UniversityHillsdale CollegeHollins UniversityHoward University School of LawJames Madison UniversityJohns Hopkins UniversityKansas State UniversityKenyon CollegeKings' College, UKKing’s College LondonLehigh UniversityLondon Business SchoolLondon School of EconomicsLondon University, Queen Mary and Westfield CollegeLouisiana State UniversityLouisiana State University Law CenterLoyola University Chicago School of LawLoyola University New Orleans School of LawMarquette UniversityMassachusetts Institute of TechnologyMemorial University of NewfoundlandMissouri University of Science and TechnologyMount Saint Mary's CollegeMurdoch University, Perth, AustraliaNew York UniversityNew York University School of LawNew York University, College of Arts and SciencesNew York University, Leonard N. Stern School of BusinessNewcastle UniversityNorth Carolina State UniversityNorthumbria University NewcastleNorthwestern UniversityNorthwestern University School of LawNottingham Law SchoolOhio Wesleyan UniversityOklahoma State UniversityOld Dominion UniversityOslo Metropolitan UniversityOxford Institute of Legal PracticeOxford UniversityPace UniversityPepperdine UniversityPrinceton UniversityQueens CollegeRandolph-Macon CollegeReed CollegeRhodes CollegeRice UniversityRipon CollegeRutgers School of LawSaint Olaf CollegeSaint-Joseph UniversitySam Houston State UniversitySanta Clara University School of LawSeattle Pacific UniversitySeattle University School of LawSeoul National UniversitySewanee: The University Of The SouthSouth Texas College of Law HoustonSouthern Methodist UniversitySouthern Methodist University Dedman School of LawSouthern Methodist University,
Meadows School of the ArtsSouthern Methodist University, Dedman CollegeSouthern Methodist University, School of EngineeringSt. Catharine’s College, University of CambridgeSt. Edward's UniversitySt. John's University School of LawSt. Mary's UniversitySt. Mary's University School of LawStanford Law SchoolStanford UniversityStephen F. Austin State UniversitySwarthmore CollegeSyracuse UniversityTemple University Beasley School of LawTexas A&M UniversityTexas Christian UniversityTexas State UniversityThe Catholic University of AmericaThe College of Law, ChesterThe College of Law, LondonThe College of New JerseyThe George Washington UniversityThe George Washington University Law SchoolThe National Law Center, George Washington UniversityThe Pennsylvania State UniversityThe UCLA School of LawThe University of Alabama School of LawThe University of ArizonaThe University of California at Los Angeles School of LawThe University of Chicago Law SchoolThe University of DenverThe University of Denver, Daniels College of BusinessThe University of GeorgiaThe University of KansasThe University of LawThe University of LiverpoolThe University of Louisiana at LafayetteThe University of ManchesterThe University of MississippiThe University of Mississippi School of LawThe University of OklahomaThe University of Southwestern LouisianaThe University of St. Thomas School of EducationThe University of Texas at ArlingtonThe University of Texas at AustinThe University of Texas at DallasThe University of Texas at San AntonioThe University of Texas School of LawThurgood Marshall School of LawTransylvania University in Lexington, KentuckyTrinity College, Hartford, ConnecticutTrinity UniversityTufts UniversityTufts University, The Fletcher School of Law & DiplomacyTulane UniversityTulane University Law SchoolU.S. Military Academy at West PointUniversidad Anahuac Mexico NorteUniversidad de SevillaUniversidad IberoamericanaUniversidad Panamericana, Mexico CityUniversité Jean Moulin Lyon Ill, FranceUniversité Paris-Sorbonne (Paris IV)University at Albany – State University of New YorkUniversity at BuffaloUniversity College DublinUniversity College LondonUniversity of Aberdeen and University of HelsinkiUniversity of Akron School of LawUniversity of AlabamaUniversity of Baltimore School of LawUniversity of BristolUniversity of CalgaryUniversity of California, Berkeley School of LawUniversity of California, Santa CruzUniversity of Cambridge, EnglandUniversity of Cambridge, Magdalene CollegeUniversity of Cape TownUniversity of Central ArkansasUniversity of Chicago Graduate School of BusinessUniversity of Cincinnati College of LawUniversity of Cincinnati College-Conservatory of MusicUniversity of ColoradoUniversity of Connecticut
School of LawUniversity of DelawareUniversity of DenverUniversity of Denver Sturm College of LawUniversity of EdinburghUniversity of FloridaUniversity of GlasgowUniversity of HeidelbergUniversity of HoustonUniversity of Houston Law CenterUniversity of Houston-Clear LakeUniversity of IllinoisUniversity of KansasUniversity of Kansas School of LawUniversity of KwaZulu-Natal, Howard CollegeUniversity of LawUniversity of Law, LondonUniversity of LondonUniversity of Louisville School of LawUniversity of MarylandUniversity of Maryland College ParkUniversity of Maryland School of LawUniversity of MassachusettsUniversity of MiamiUniversity of MichiganUniversity of Michigan Law SchoolUniversity of MinnesotaUniversity of Minnesota Law SchoolUniversity of MissouriUniversity of MysoreUniversity of New South Wales, AustraliaUniversity of New South Wales, Sydney, AustraliaUniversity of Newcastle Upon TyneUniversity of North Carolina at AshevilleUniversity of North Carolina at Chapel Hill School of LawUniversity of North TexasUniversity of Notre DameUniversity of NottinghamUniversity of OklahomaUniversity of Oklahoma College of LawUniversity of Ottawa, Common Law ProgramUniversity of PennsylvaniaUniversity of Pennsylvania Law SchoolUniversity of Pittsburgh Swanson School of EngineeringUniversity of Poitiers, FranceUniversity of ReadingUniversity of RichmondUniversity of RochesterUniversity of San DiegoUniversity of Southern CaliforniaUniversity of St AndrewsUniversity of St. ThomasUniversity of TasmaniaUniversity of Tulsa College of LawUniversity of Tulsa Collins College of BusinessUniversity of UtahUniversity of VermontUniversity of VirginiaUniversity of Virginia School of LawUniversity of WarwickUniversity of WashingtonUniversity of Western Australia, Perth, AustraliaUniversity of Wisconsin Law SchoolUniversity of Wisconsin-MadisonUS Army John F. Kennedy Special Warfare CenterVanderbilt UniversityVanderbilt University Law SchoolVermont Law SchoolVillanova University School of LawWashington and Lee UniversityWashington and Lee University School of LawWashington University in St. LouisWellesley CollegeWesleyan UniversityWidener University Law SchoolWilliams CollegeYale Law SchoolYale UniversityYeshiva University
Not looking for a lawyer? Browse Firm Administration and Paralegals.
Industries
Energy
Finance
Healthcare
Infrastructure
Real Estate
Technology
Practices
Industries
IndustriesEnergyFinanceHealthcareInfrastructureReal EstateTechnology
Practices
PracticesAntitrust / CompetitionCorporate & Securities-- Capital Markets-- Corporate Governance & Compliance-- Mergers, Acquisitions & Divestitures-- MLPsEmployee Benefits / ERISAEnergy Regulations-- Commodities & Trading-- Compliance & Enforcement-- Electric Power-- Oil & Gas TransactionsEnvironmental Strategies-- Litigation & Enforcement Defense-- Natural Resource Protection-- Permitting & Regulation-- Pipeline Safety & Regulation-- Transaction Diligence & SupportFinancial Institutions-- Banking Compliance & Enforcement-- Mergers & AcquisitionsGovernment Contracts-- Suspension and DebarmentGovernment Enforcement & Investigations-- Cybersecurity-- FCPA-- Internal InvestigationsGovernment Relations-- Lobbying-- Political Law & Compliance CounselIncident Prevention & Response-- Business Continuity Planning-- Crisis Communications-- Facilitating Emergency Drills & Tabletops-- OSHA/Workplace Safety-- Process Safety-- The Chemical Safety BoardInfrastructure & Development-- Energy Infrastructure-- Social Infrastructure-- Transportation InfrastructureIntellectual Property-- Data Security and Privacy-- Patents-- Technology Transactions-- Trademark / CopyrightsLabor & Employment-- Agreements-- Class & Collective Actions-- Compliance-- Employment Litigation-- Immigration-- OSHA-- UnionsLending-- Asset-Based Lending-- Mezzanine Lending-- Project Finance-- Reserve-Based Lending-- Structured Finance, Commodities Finance & Derivative Products-- Syndicated LendingLitigation-- Appellate-- Construction Litigation-- Employment-- Energy Litigation-- Environmental Litigation-- Financial Institutions Litigation-- International Energy Disputes-- IP Litigation-- Securities & Corporate Governance LitigationOil & Gas-- Exploration & Production-- Midstream-- Oil & Gas Private Equity-- Oil & Gas Trading & Marketing-- Refining & Petrochemicals-- Water IndustryOutsourcingPower-- Independent Power Producers-- Power Private Equity-- Power Trading & Marketing-- Regulated UtilitiesPrivate EquityPublic Finance-- Bond Counsel-- Disclosure Counsel-- Economic Development / Project Finance-- Securities Enforcement-- Tax Counsel-- Underwriter’s CounselReal Estate Investment & Finance-- Acquisitions & Divestitures-- Commercial & Mixed Use Development-- Project Finance & LendingRenewable Energy & Sustainability -- Biomass-- Carbon Capture Utilization and Storage -- Energy Storage -- Hydrogen-- Hydropower-- Solar-- WindStrategic CommunicationsTaxTax Exempt Organizations
Lawyers
All LawyersJay AldisRona Amigues-MacRaeWilliam S. AndersonJeffrey B. AndrewsWilliam T. AvilaC. Robert BairdRebecca L. BakerShannon BaldwinDavid J. BallJonathan BatesMargaret B. BeasleyLance W. BehnkeW. Stephen BeneshBradley J. BenoitW. Jared BergPhilip J. BezansonKeith BlackmanAdam BlytheGregory M. BoppElizabeth Rippy BowesTracey L. BradleyStephen L. BragaJohn R. BrantleyMichael W. BrooksIan R. BrownSara M. BurginAnna BurhopRobert G. BurnsLeslie Selig ByrdOlivia CaddySylvia CheremBrad Y. ChinPeggy B. ChristmanRobert L. ClarkeJason G. CohenKevin D. CollinsRobert R. Collins IIIDaniel S. ConnollyStephen B. CrainMary CurryNancy McEvily DavisKate H. DayLilliana DealbertTim J. DeithloffKirsty DelaneyG. Adam DempseyMark E. DendingerKeith R. DerringtonAmber K. DoddsChristopher L. DodsonLiam P. DonovanChristopher L. DrymallaBryan S. DumesnilRyan M. ElettoDina
ElshurafaCatherine B. EngellKevin A. EwingGeorge D. FatulaGeorge D. FelcynBlakely FernandezEdward FierroJordan K. FineJason FoxJonathan K. FrelsDanielle GarbienVictoria M. GarciaTimothy R. GeigerSteven H. GerdesJohn
GilbertShannon E. GlenGene E. GodleyRachel B. GoldmanDewey J. Gonsoulin Jr.Sean GormanR. Todd GreenwaltMatthew B. GrunertAmy Karff HalevyJonathon K. HanceShelby HardenTroy L. HarderDaniel E. HemliYvonne Y. HoJeffrey R. HolmsteadNina HowellStephen J. HugR. Joe HullJason B. HuttOliver IrwinLisa M. JaegerBen JamesJacqueline R. JavaJason M. JeanTyler S. JohnsonBarbara S. JonesBrittney E.
JusticeMartha KammounDeanna E. KingJames H. Kizziar Jr.Joshua
KleinYeon Jae Ko, Ph.D.Thomas F. KokalasAndrej Kormuth Logan S.
KotlerEdward D. KrenikEric S. LaiJay N. LarryJoseph T.
LasherJonathan C. LeatherberryAustin T. LeeJohn LeeMark K. LewisDon J. LonczakTracy LondonSteven J. LorchClark Stockton LordPaul S. MacoJane H. MaconFrank V. MaisanoEdgar J. Marston IIIE. Dee MartinBenjamin J. MartinCatherine P. McCarthyElizabeth L. McGinleyKate Barrington McGregorJoshua T. McNultyRobert MeadeKathy Witty MedfordCaroline Melo Robin J. MilesAndrew W. MonkVincent E. MorganD. Kirk Morgan IIWilliam A. MossAde MosuroEimear MurphyShayan
Najib Bagyasree NambronPaul NathansonAnn
D. NavaroAngela W. NeSmithNicholas NeubergerRobert S. NicholsMatthew G. NielsenChristopher D. OliveGary W. OrloffVictoria N. OzimekPriyanka PatelMatt PaulsonRobert E. PeaseBrittany M. PembertonKathryn F. PenryDavid M. PerlmanOliver PhillipsDavid R. PoeDaniel J. PopeBenjamin Pridgeon Andrew T. PrihodaAdam QuigleyG. Alan RafteChristopher H. RentzelConstance Gall RhebergenEdmund W. RobbJoshua Robichaud Fernando J. Rodriguez MarinLowell M. RothschildPhillip L. Sampson Jr.Scott C. SandersNicolai J. SaradScott H. SegalJonathan L. SeligerVivek P. Shankam, Ph.D.David A. ShargelChristopher A. ShieldBoris ShkutaCaitlin SicklesDarren SpaldingDavid
B.
SpringerJohn L. Stavinoha IIIBritt Cass SteckmanDouglas F. StewartClint SteynCharles H. Still Jr.David
A. SuperTom SwarbrickWhit SwiftDrew TaggartKevin R. TammBrian P. TeaffJ. Anthony TerrellCatherine ToddBrian H. TompkinsMiles Tonkin Paula
Toro Chris TravisLucy TysonTimothy J. UrbanBlake UrbanJeffery B. VadenManuel VeraTony L. VisageKevin M. VoelkelRobert J. Wagman Jr.Barron F. WallaceAdam WaszkiewiczRichard F. WhiteleyTimothy A. WilkinsChristopher R. WilliamsStacianne M. WilsonWilliam A. Wood IIIChristine
G. WymanAlastair YoungAndrew W. ZeveJoshua C. Zive
Privacy Notice
1. INTRODUCTION
Bracewell LLP and Bracewell (UK) LLP (collectively, "Bracewell" / "we" / "us" / "our") provide this Privacy Notice to inform you of our policy relating to the processing of your personal information. We take your privacy seriously and we are committed to protecting personal data that we receive from you. This Privacy Notice sets out the basis on which we will process your personal information. Please read it carefully to understand our practices regarding your personal information and how we will use it.
If you reside in the EU, the data controller (as defined under EU data protection law) will be the Bracewell relevant entity with whom you engage.
Contacting us
If you have any questions about this privacy notice, your personal information, or would like to exercise any rights that you may have in relation to your personal data, please contact us at privacy@bracewell.com.
2.   What types of data are protected
A. Personal data
This Privacy Notice applies to your personal data, which is any information relating to you as an identified or identifiable person. For purposes of this Privacy Notice, your personal data may also be referred to as personal information.
B. Special categories of personal data
We recognize that in certain contexts, we may collect personal data from one or more of the “special categories of personal data” (as defined under EU data protection laws) which are subject to a greater degree of protection.
3. What Information we Process
The processing activities we engage in with respect to personal data you provide to the us depends on the nature of our exchanges with you.
A. Personal information we process
We may process one or more of the following types of personal information, depending on the context:
Interactions with our website
Name
Personal contact details (e.g., personal email address, personal address, telephone number(s))
Company contact details (e.g., company name, position, business email address, business address, telephone number(s))
Interactions as our client or as an aspect of the client engagement process
Name
Personal contact details (e.g., personal email address, personal address, telephone number(s))
Company contact details (e.g., company name, position, business email address, business address, telephone number(s))
Information relating to the matter that is the subject of the engagement or potential engagement
Information provided by you in support of or incidental to the engagement or potential engagement
Documents related to identification information
Documents related to financial information for servicing the engagement
Information required to comply with our legal obligations
Interactions related to event invitations, updates, or other marketing materials
Name
Personal contact details (e.g., personal email address, personal address, telephone number(s))
Company contact details (e.g., company name, position, business email address, business address, telephone number(s))
Communication preferences (e.g., type, frequency, feedback, continuation)
Information collected through alumni relationship
Information collected through our e-mail systems (e.g., opening emails, clicking links in emails)
Other information, such as for purposes of attending an event or for purposes of providing feedback
Interactions with us during the recruitment process
Contact details (e.g., personal, business or educational institution email address, telephone numbers, address)
Resumé, including relevant skills and experience
Passport, work permit, visa, or other immigration documentation
Results of background checks including references, qualifications, and to the extent permitted by law, criminal background checks
Application reasons
Language capabilities
Special requirements, such as, or relating to, a disability / health issue
Other personal data provided during the recruitment process
B. Personal data that we may collect through cookies
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard-drive for record-keeping purposes.
Bracewell uses cookies on its website to obtain web analytics from third-party vendors. These third parties use cookies to help analyze how users use the website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transferred to and stored by third-party vendors on servers in the United States. These vendors will use this information for the purposes of analyzing your use of the website, creating reports on the website activity, and providing other services relating to the website activity. These vendors may also transfer this information to other third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on the vendor's behalf.
You can refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, though please note that if you do so, you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Bracewell website.
4. What we do with your information and on what basis
A. Ways we process your personal data
We may process your personal data in one or more of following ways:
Collecting your personal data, such as through our website, from conversations, emails, or meetings with us, or from third parties.
Recording your personal data, such as through electronic or handwritten notes that we make.
Organizing and storing your personal data, such as on our servers, in our management systems, in our electronic HR systems, in our employee's email inbox folders, with cloud-based services, or in hard copy files.
Using your personal data, such as to provide our services to you or to your employer, or address any preferences, complaints, or comments that you have.
Disclosing your personal data within the firm or to third parties, such as where necessary, appropriate and/or as required by law (see section 5 providing more information on this below).
B. Our purposes for processing your personal data
We may process your personal data for one or more of the following purposes:
To process and manage the provision of our services to you or to your employer
To create and deliver personalized communications that are relevant to your preferences
To provide invitations to events or other sponsored meetings
To facilitate the recruitment process
To respond to your questions, comments, complaints, or requests
To facilitate the recruitment process
To comply with our legal obligations
C. Legal basis for processing your personal data
We may process your personal data on one or more of the following bases:
Consent
To perform under a contract with you
To comply with our legal obligations
In pursuit of our legitimate interests
Our legitimate interests include one or more of the following:
Supporting client representations, including business communications
Complying with our ethical obligations
Maintaining and managing our subscription offerings
Maintaining and managing our communications with you
Expanding our service offerings
Growing our business
Expanding our professional networks
Consideration for future employment
5. DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION
We take your privacy seriously and will not share your personal data with others, except in the following circumstances:
Service providers – we may disclose your personal data to third-party service providers, such as website hosting, information technology services, payroll services, auditing services, consultancy services, regulatory services, and legal services in other countries.
Our affiliated offices – we may disclose your personal data to our other group entities in order to provide you or your employer with tailored services and communications, or in accordance with our business administrative practices.
Government Agencies – we may disclosure your personal data to government agencies as required, for example to provide services, at your direction, or at the direction of your employer.
To fulfill your option to share our website content with third parties – using the sharing features on our website (to share content with Facebook, LinkedIn, or Twitter, for example).
Legal reasons – we may use or disclose your personal data as we deem necessary or appropriate under applicable laws.
International transfers of personal data
Some of our affiliated offices and service providers are located in the United States. Accordingly, please note that we will transfer personal data from our non-US offices to the United States in accordance with data protection law requirements by using standard contractual clauses that have been approved by the European Commission.
6. RETAINING YOUR DATA
We retain your personal data in accordance with our retention policies, and in accordance with applicable laws. The actual retention period for your personal data depends on the nature of our exchanges with you.  We do not collect more personal data than we need to fulfill our purposes stated in this privacy policy.
7. WHAT RIGHTS DO YOU HAVE WITH RESPECT TO YOUR PERSONAL DATA?
If you are a client of Bracewell (UK) LLP or an EU resident, you may have the following rights with respect to the personal data you provide to us, to the extent permitted by applicable data protection laws:
a) To withdraw any consent that you have provided to us to process your personal data.
b) To access or rectify your personal data.
c) To have your personal data erased if it is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was processed; you have withdrawn your consent to its processing; or you object to its processing and there is no overriding legitimate interest to continue its processing.
d) To have the processing of your personal data restricted if you contest its accuracy, its processing is unlawful, we no longer need it but you need it for a legal claim, or you have objected to its processing and await verification of our legitimate grounds for processing it.
e) To have your personal data transferred to another company under certain circumstances.
f) To complain to your national data protection regulator if you feel that your personal data has been unlawfully processed.
To make inquiry regarding these rights or to make a request with regard to one of these rights, please contact privacy@bracewell.com. Please be prepared to provide information that will allow us to confirm your identity and indicate the nature of our exchanges with you, e.g., client context, solely marketing context. By providing us this information it will enable us to better respond to your inquiry.
8. HOW WILL WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA?
We have implemented security policies and technical measures to protect the personal data that we collect, consistent with applicable privacy and security laws. These security measures are designed to prevent unauthorized access, improper use or disclosure, unauthorized modification, and unlawful destruction or accidental loss of your personal data.
We update and test our personal data privacy and security measures on an ongoing basis. We also provide training to our employees on privacy laws and how to comply with them. We ensure that only employees who need to know your personal data to fulfill the purposes of processing that personal data (as described in this privacy policy) have access to it.
9. LINKS TO THIRD-PARTY SITES
Our website may include links to other sites operated by third parties. We are not responsible for information on these sites, nor for services or products offered by them. Use of such sites, including transmitting your personal data to them, is at your own risk. You should check the privacy policies (and other applicable terms and conditions) of these third-party sites.
10. CHANGES
We review our privacy practices on an ongoing basis, and as such we may change this privacy policy from time to time. If such change includes any significant, material changes, we will provide clear notice of the update on the homepage of our website. Please check this policy frequently to ensure that you are familiar with its current content.
This privacy policy was last updated on May 23, 2018.
